movixhub.com 2016-12-01

# privacy-policy - MovixHub

PRIVACY POLICY

movixhub.com (the "Site" or "We" or "Us") allows you to easily create your own fully functional Movies and TV shows site in minutes with zero coding knowledge.

This privacy policy sets out any information you provide us when you use the site. Together, with movixhub.com Terms of Service ("Terms") – those are the accesses and terms of your use in the site.

As used in this privacy policy, “Information” means information that can be directly associated with a specific person or entity such as a name, address, telephone number, or e-mail address. Other terms capitalized but not defined in this Privacy Policy shall have the meaning set forth in our Terms of Service at www. movixhub.com (the “Terms”).

Information We Collect

The types of information we gather:

Information you provide: We receive and store any information you enter on movixhub.com or give us in any other way. You might be asked to log in to your account (it can be Google or Facebook account and etc.) in order to generate your user identifier in movixhub.com systems and to personalize your experience while using movixhub.com. We may collect your name, email address, country of origin, and, if you choose, your nickname, telephone number, website, company, and title. Demographic information may be correlated to web usage information collected during your use of the service. In addition, you might provide us with personal identifying information, such as mobile telephone number, when you communicate with us by phone, e-mail or otherwise, or complete a questionnaire, subscription form or a contest entry form. You can choose not to provide certain information, but then you might not be able to take advantage of many of our features. We use the information that you provide for such purposes as responding to your requests, customizing and improving our services, delivering targeted content and advertisements that may be of interest to you, and communicating with you.

Automatic information we collect from the site: We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with our site. For example, like many websites, we use "cookies," and we obtain certain types of information when your Web browser accesses the Site. Examples of the information we may collect and analyze when you use our website include the IP address used to connect your computer to the Internet; computer and connection information such as browser type, version, and time zone setting;

Information Sharing

We do not sell your personal information to third parties. However, we may disclose your personal information:

As required by law such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process.

When we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request.

If movixhub.com is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information.

To any other third party with your prior consent to do so.

Anchor We do not record any calls that you make using movixhub.com.

Use of Information

movixhub.com may use information (whether personal identifying information or not) that we collect about you to:

Manage your relationship with us and provide you with customer support.

Perform research and analysis about your use of, or interest in, our products, services or content, or products, services or content offered by others.

Communicate with you by e-mail, postal mail, telephone and/or mobile devices about products or services that may be of interest to you either from us or third parties.

Cooperate with legal, criminal or regulatory investigations or proceedings.

Manage our business.

Enforce our Agreement.

Linked Content

Certain sections of the site may involve sites which belongs to third parties. movixhub.com is not and shall not be responsible for that, and any use by the user of the sites belonging to third parties is in his sole responsibility. Therefore, movixhub.com will not be responsible for actions that occurred at sites belonging to third parties. Moreover, movixhub.com warns from sites belonging to third parties and offers the user to read carefully the terms of use of those sites.

Security

When we collect personal information directly from you, we follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can contact us.

Notification of Privacy Statement Changes

We may update this privacy statement to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.

Contact Information

You can contact us about this privacy statement by emailing us at: support@movixhub.com
